In the past years,
no one else stayed with me.
I want to be your wife.
I think it's because he's been too busy.
You haven't had enough sleep
because you're busy preparing
for the premiere night, right?
I'm glad you accepted my offer
to give our friendship a second chance, Liam.
We should communicate to the voters
that I should continue
the good things I've started.
Thank you so much, everyone.
I'm so glad
to see you all happy and complete.
What are...
You're the man who's always in my dreams.
I saw I was shot.
I felt that I died.
I saw that I got shot.
I felt that...
I died.
Babe... babe, look at me. Look at me.
What's going on?
Joyce.
I died.
I saw it. I felt that... I died.
Babe, relax.
Don't think about...
Please get her some water.
Miss, please give me some water.
Liam, what's happening?
What did you do to Joyce?
Do you plan to scare her to death?
- I didn't do anything.
- I saw it.
I saw... I saw it like it really happened.
I saw that we were shooting a scene...
I was shot. I died. It felt so real.
I felt that I died.
Babe, have some water first.
Calm down, babe.
Miss Joyce, don't say that.
Knock on wood.
Don't say that.
I'm the one handling the props.
I'm not joking. I'm telling the truth.
I saw it, Liam. You!
You're the man who's always in my dreams.
You're telling me something.
Joyce, I'm... I'm sorry.
But I don't know what you're talking about.
What?
Miss Joyce, it's just a dream.
Let's all relax.
Death in a dream might mean,
you know, just the end of something.
Just like our movie that concluded.
And also the beginning of something new.
Maybe we'll have a new project. Right?
New work?
But you said you've been
dreaming of Sir Liam.
Right, Miss Joyce?
What's your interpretation of it, Megan?
I don't want to interpret it.
Guys, please.
Can we not get ahead of ourselves?
Should we call a witch doctor?
Someone might have put a curse on you.
It's scary.
I don't know. I feel dizzy.
Dear, is there a problem?
Breathe.
Hey, babe. Baby, look at me.
Babe.
Sorry.
Just like Mom,
she remembers the events I altered
using the typewriter.
You're experiencing it too, Joyce.
Is it because you and Mom are alike?
Was it wrong to change what happened?
What has changed, Liam?
The last time we talked, Liam,
you told me you knew the real reason
behind what happened to Uncle Edmond.
This has to do with
my investigation of Casa Fuerte.
Now, tell me.
Why...
Why did you change your mind?
I'm sorry, Hans.
Maybe...
maybe it was just my writer's instinct...
that I want everything
to have an explanation.
First of all, I don't have proof.
I might only make things more complicated.
Sorry if...
I put ideas in your head.
But I'll leave everything to you for now.
Liam, I can't just ignore what you said.
We're talking about the reason
why my fiancée's father went blind.
Liam.
Liam!
Are you and Liam talking about me?
No, Uncle.
Hans.
Thank you for your concern,
but listen to me carefully.
You're marrying my daughter.
You should focus on that.
I want you and Joyce to be happy...
and have a peaceful life.
- Uncle Edmond...
- Promise me this, Hans.
You will protect my daughter.
You will keep her away from harm.
Your job is dangerous.
You know that.
You might be going
against someone influential.
And I don't want my daughter to get involved.
Uncle...
I love your daughter so much.
I will do everything.
I will protect her more than my own life.
I promise you that.
The program is about to start.
Let's go back to our seats.
Go ahead. I'll just get some fresh air.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Go on. Go with Joyce.
- Babe...
- Let's go, babe.
Uncle.
I won't come forward, Lando.
Keep my daughter out of this.
The problem, Edmond,
is you know too much.
You see too much.
You should go blind.
Lando, don't!
Don't!
Good evening, guys.
I know the success we're enjoying right now
didn't come easy.
We worked hard for this film.
More than that is...
the inspiration that...
our co-workers gave us.
Like the kids in Bahay Aruga Orphanage.
Especially Sep.
Yes!
Sep for the win!
Sir Liam.
Are you okay?
What? Of course. I'm excited to see Sep.
Liam.
That's why...
we offer this celebration...
for the kid who made
the whole production smile.
To Stefano Lualhati,
also known as Sep.
Yes! Go, Sep! That's my boy!
Leroy.
What's going on?
Why are we having this? Where's Sep?
Liam, what's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
Joyce, I don't know where Sep is.
- Where's Sep?
- Liam.
- What's happening?
- Liam, that is inappropriate for the kids.
Inappropriate? I'm looking for Sep.
Where is he?
Let's talk later, please.
What?
Joy...
Rest in power, Stefano Lualhati.
What? Borj, what are you saying?
What do you mean by that?
What are you talking about?
What's going on?
Liam, sit down first.
Days have gone by so fast.
It has been 40 days since his death.
The reason why...
we celebrate both the success of our film...
and Sep's life,
is because of the deal Liam and I have.
We agreed...
that part of the film's proceeds would go
to the Bahay Aruga Orphanage.
Since that day,
I have the desire in my heart
to help the kids.
I know that...
it was a short journey for Sep.
But many people love him.
Joyce... Joyce, wait.
A short journey?
What's this? What is happening?
- Is this a prank?
- Liam.
Are you joking?
- I can't understand.
- Liam, what are you doing?
What am I doing? I'm confused.
I don't know what's going on here.
Tell me, what's happening? Where's Sep?
Sister, where's Sep?
Liam, Liam...
Sep is gone, dear.
No... Sister, that's not true.
Sister, don't tell me...
- Sep is not dead!
- Liam!
Sep is already dead.
Please, Liam, calm down.
Liam.
Liam...
I'm sorry.
I don't know what's happening to Liam.
No, no, no.
This can't be.
It can't be. Sep can't die. No.
Why can't I remember? Why...
Why do these things happen
whenever I use the typewriter?
No!
Liam, come on!
Liam, calm down!
Joyce.
Joyce, sorry.
Sorry, I don't know anymore.
Liam... What's going on with you?
Make me understand What's happening...
Joyce, I'm confused too.
I don't understand.
You told me to celebrate
Sep's 40th day of passing...
You said Sep didn't want us to be sad.
What's going on with you?
Joyce, how did Sep die?
Liam, what's with you?
Why don't you seem to remember anything?
Come on!
Tell me, please.
How did Sep die?
Heart failure, Liam.
We've known for a long time
that Sep was sick.
Why wasn't he brought to the hospital?
The doctor talked to the both of us.
Cardiomyopathy.
Sep got it from his father.
Sep was already dead
when the nuns found him.
Does it mean...
Sep died alone?
Sep was alone when he died?
Liam, what...
Son, get up...
It's already late in the morning,
yet your room is still so dark.
Mom.
I thought you would wake up
from the smell of the breakfast I cooked.
Son? I made sure it's good.
Mom, please close the window.
The light is blinding me.
I also feel sad.
I have learned to love Sep, too.
It's so hard, Mom.
I'm having a hard time.
It feels like my heart went numb.
It feels so heavy.
I feel like drowning.
It's so hard to breathe.
Son.
You can't let your heart stop from beating.
It's like...
forgetting that Sep existed.
He taught you how to love, didn't he?
So if you keep loving,
Sep continues to live.
Son.
Are you really okay now, Love?
Don't worry about me.
Love, please don't push me away.
I understand.
I want to grieve with you.
I know how close you were with Sep.
Thank you.
Look at you. You're still cold.
Can't you be a little sweeter?
This is your favorite, right?
I'm not hungry yet.
I got scared.
I only wanted to protect my dad.
I'm the reason...
I'm the reason Joyce died.
How about you, Via?
What's the worst you can do out of hatred?
Love, stop talking that way.
You don't need to be angry with anyone.
We all know that Sep was sick.
But you're the reason
I had to use the typewriter again.
Joyce is alive, but Sep is dead.
I'm sorry, Via,
if I can no longer look at you like before.
Anyway.
I came here to ask
if you can attend the meeting
with Dad tomorrow.
For his campaign?
Honestly, I don't know
why I accepted that project.
That's a no, then.
Don't worry.
I'll just explain it to Dad.
Love.
We're okay, right?
I know you're going through a lot.
I hope you won't let it
affect our relationship.
Please, keep me out of it.
I'm not doing anything wrong.
Isn't that unfair?
You're taking it out on me.
I don't think I deserve that.
Liam, I love you.
I hope you still love me too.
[Bahay Aruga Orphanage]
Eat slowly.
Is it good?
Son, are you sure you're okay
to come back here so soon?
You might miss Sep even more.
Mom...
I have learned to love these kids.
And as you said,
as long as my heart is full of love,
I will never forget Sep.
Mama Tess, your spaghetti is so good.
Wow!
Really? Did you like it?
- Yes.
- Oh, thank you!
Go on. Eat some more.
Sir Liam, let's do TikTok.
Sir Liam.
Miss Joyce, let's do TikTok.
Cupid's arrow hit me.
- Are you in love?
Sorry, I can't.
I'll do it with you. Is it okay?
Can you teach me how?
- Yes.
- Really? Come on.
I don't know how to do it.
Can you show me? How do we do it?
You do it like this.
Wow! That was good!
Who else knows how to do it?
Come on, let's do TikTok.
I want to see it!
Go on. Please, show me how.
Game!
I want to be near Mom and Dad
when I become a star.
I will watch over you.
I promise Miss Joyce,
your mom, and your dad
that I will watch over you.
Sorry, Sep.
I couldn't fulfill my promise
to take care of you.
Now, you're gone.
I can't even remember
what happened to you.
I'm sorry...
I chose to save Joyce's life.
Sir Liam, I wish I was a star.
Why?
So even if my parents die early,
I would have already spent millions of years
with them.
I don't know
if you're my son's reincarnation.
Is fate playing tricks on me?
I can't understand anymore.
I know you're not Dex.
But I've learned to love you
like my own son, Sep.
Sister.
Have you seen Liam?
No.
Maybe he's here.
Liam?
Joyce?
Mom and I visited the kids.
Sister and I have something to discuss.
I can still hear Sep's laughter in my head...
And his witty remarks.
He will forever be on our minds...
and in our hearts.
Hi, Sister.
- Liam, son. I've been looking for you.
- Aunt Tess.
- Mom.
- Joyce.
Good morning.
So you and Sister are here, Miss Joyce.
Can we start the meeting?
Wait. Meeting?
I want to know
what other assistance the orphanage needs
to make the kids' situation better.
Sister, you wanted to see us?
Yes.
This is Lerna and Arnel. They're a couple.
Lerna is my secretary
and Arnel is our all-around boy.
And this is Liam and Joyce.
They will help us renovate the orphanage.
Really? They're going to help us?
We're so glad to hear that.
We can't do it on our own.
Sister, can you tell us
the estimated cost of the renovation?
It's more or less...
I will help.
And Borj, too.
You need manpower, right?
Of course, Liam.
Okay.
The more help we get, the better.
Okay, I will also tell Deedee and Leroy
while they're not yet busy.
I'll take care of your food.
Thank you so much.
You are heaven-sent.
We can start
as soon as I buy everything we need.
Aren't you busy, dear?
Like I said, I always have time
for you, the kids, and Sep.
Children, enough running.
You might get hurt.
That's enough.
Yes, Sister.
I'm sorry you had to see that, Liam.
It's okay.
Kids are really stubborn.
But it feels good to watch them.
But sometimes they make us
lose our poise.
We earn negative points up there.
I don't know.
I've become anxious since Sep died.
I can't help but remember
the night Sister Pam and I
found him unconscious.
He was gone when we brought him
to the hospital.
I'm sorry if that was such a downer.
If only I could do something for Sep.
I still blame myself for what happened.
Sister, no one wanted it to happen.
I don't know, Liam.
If only we found him earlier.
That night, we heard him screaming.
He sounded like he was fighting with someone.
And when we went out,
we found him on the ground unconscious.
But you know what's puzzling?
When we went out of the gate,
it smelled like gasoline.
Sister.
It smelled like gasoline?
And you found Sep outside unconscious?
Uncle Ramon.
I didn't know you were here.
Sorry, I was busy.
How does it feel to be
the new CEO of Casa Fuerte?
I owe you big time, Uncle Ramon.
Danilo isn't getting any younger.
This office needs a new monster.
Someone hungry.
Someone who wants to prove himself.
Well, Uncle Ramon, I'm your man.
You're the man.
Really?
I wonder why you still
haven't done what I asked you.
To acquire the land of
the Bahay Aruga Orphanage.
Just give me time, Uncle Ramon.
You'll get your hands
on that property eventually.
Make sure of that, Vergil.
I'm not the type of man
who patiently waits to get what he wants.
[Bahay Aruga Orphanage]
Boss Bro!
I thought we'll be on full force?
Looks like we're in trouble.
Are you saying something, Borj?
Megan, if this is filming
and you're the first to arrive,
you'll be complaining, too.
There they are.
Have you started already?
Sorry, Borj.
We first made sure we had all the materials.
And we talked to the kids, too.
They said they are going to help.
The kids are going to help?
How?
Kids!
Come on, let's go downstairs. Careful, okay?
Careful.
Hello!
Are you happy?
Yes!
Are you excited?
- Okay, let's go.
- We've got lots of helpers.
Are your hands ready?
Ready?
Be careful, kids.
Don't get too excited.
Careful.
Hey, are you just going
to keep standing there?
Why don't you help us?
Deedee, work the wall.
Leroy, come here.
- Why are you and Leroy together?
- Right, right.
- The wall is too high.
- I should be with Leroy.
Later. Come over here.
You're too happy.
It's not just the kids who are happy.
You made us happy, too.
Anything for the kids.
Anything for Sep's friends.
We want them to learn the value
of helping each other.
When you're home,
there's no one else you can count on
but your family.
You're right, Miss Joyce.
It's not bad to get help.
But like we always do,
we draw strength from each other.
Oh, by the way, Liam,
let's go see that thing you asked me about.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Where are you going?
Arnel and I will check
what else we have to fix here.
Okay. Don't take too long, okay?
You can't run away from work.
We still have a lot to paint.
Yes, Ma'am.
You don't want to lose sight of him, huh?
We're just friends, Lerna.
Yes. We're just friends.
Okay. If you say so.
Just draw it on the wall.
Hey.
- Come on.
- Let's go.
Babe.
Here. There's CCTV over there.
And there's another one there.
But they are not working.
Both have been defective.
We don't have budget for the repair.
Does it mean it did not capture anything?
Nothing. It's just for display...
To scare off crooks.
They can't get anything
in the orphanage, anyway.
What will they get? Kids?
Sorry, that's not funny.
Why are you interested
in the CCTVs here, Liam?
Nothing.
I just want added security for the orphanage.
Oh. I thought you wanted
to check on something.
But don't worry.
I will ask the village officers
if they can fix the cameras.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Why do you ask?
I just noticed that you're with us,
but your mind is wandering somewhere else.
Is there a problem?
Joyce...
did you know that Sep was found outside?
The nuns found him unconscious.
Sister told me about that.
Why are you suddenly bringing that up?
Nothing.
I just want to know what really happened.
I understand.
It's really not easy to accept things...
especially for Sep...
who died so young.
But Liam, I hope...
I hope this charity we do for the orphanage
may help us accept his death.
Joyce, I'm sorry...
if lately I'm in a somber mood.
You don't need to apologize
for what you feel.
Even I feel the same...
Honestly, until now...
I still miss Sep.
I was thinking...
that if I have a child in the future...
if I become a mother,
I want my child to be like Sep.
Joyce...
you will be a good mother.
You think so?
You know...
My mom told me something
that I always remember whenever I miss Sep.
She told me that...
as long as I keep loving...
Sep will remain alive, here.
What do you think, Joyce?
If you're already so crushed...
do you think there is still
a chance for things to be okay?
I think...
painful things are part of our lives.
Losing someone or something
is part of our lives.
Maybe it is a reminder...
of how we should value those
who are still with us.
You're right, Joyce.
Sep's death is not meaningless.
Because he taught us how to love.
[Bahay Aruga Orphanage]
Hey, Odet!
- The hose is moving!
- Odet, there!
Hey! Hey! Boss bro!
He's the one splashing water!
You know, we should eat.
It's almost lunch break.
Yes, I'm already hungry.
And looks like you feel so hot.
- You should take a bath!
- Hey!
What was that?
- What are you doing?
- Hey!
- Wait, my shoes!
- Girl, stop it!
- Stop it, girl!
- Come on!
Odet, go get them wet!
Oh, really? Is that so? Really?
Girl! Girl!
Girl!
Joyce!
Not my lipstick! Girl, that's expensive!
Please stop!
Girl!
Girl, I'm so dirty!
- What did you do?
- Why are you getting everyone wet?
We're so dirty!
Babe! Hey! What's going on?
Guys, hello.
Why are you getting everyone wet?
Sir Hans.
- Hello.
- Why did you come here?
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Looks like you're having fun.
I'm just going to pick you up.
Sir Hans, it's so hot.
Looks like you need to take a bath!
Sir Hans! Oh my gosh!
- Oh my gosh, Sir Hans!
- I'm sorry!
- It's okay, it's okay.
- Girl, stop it.
It's okay, babe. I have extra clothes.
Wait, wait.
- Hot-ttorney for real!
- What's happening?
- Correct!
- Deedee!
Sir Hans, I heard you're a good dancer.
Can you do TikTok?
- Yes!
- No, don't!
Let's turn up the heat!
I don't know how to dance, babe.
Boss Bro is also a good dancer!
Go, Sir Liam!
- Why did I get involved?
- Go, Sir Liam!
Come on, Sir Liam!
- Sir Liam!
- I don't dance.
Boss Bro, we're waiting!
- Sir Liam!
- Liam, you do it like this.
Sir Liam!
- Like this, Liam.
- Boss Bro!
That's enough.
What's up?
They're renovating it?
Why do they have to fix it?
I'm already buying it.
I will have to answer to Uncle Ramon!
Bye!
Uncle Ramon was right.
I need to move faster.
Guys, nice to see you all. We'll go ahead.
I'll borrow my bride-to-be for now.
- So?
- Let's dance some other time.
Okay, sure.
- Bye. Be safe.
- Bye.
Go on, Joyce. We got this.
See?
Boss Bro is strong.
He pretends he's not affected.
Sorry, what?
What I mean is, we're making Hans wait.
Go on.
I'll just update you.
We'll go ahead. Come on.
Who's that?
Who?
That man who's been observing us.
Hey! What are you doing there?
Forget about that. Maybe he's just a visitor.
What if I didn't make
the big mistake I did before?
What if I dared to take a risk?
Do you know how it will affect my campaign?
Don't try to defend me
if all you think about
is your campaign as a senator.
Didn't you realize
that he cheated on your only child?
What's going on between you and Liam?
Joyce, don't you like me anymore?
I realized it's so hard to live
under everyone's watch.
Now, I have made up my decision.
I will take a break from showbiz.